Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Alphabetical Files, 1968-2001
  - Litigations - Correspondence re: Chips and Technologies Inc. and Texas Instruments Inc., Notes on Memo Pad, License Agreements from 1971-1982 re: IBM Corp., Western Electric Company Inc., National Semiconductor Corp., Fairchild Semiconductor Corp. Camera and Instrument Corp., Hitachi Ltd., Hewlett-Packard Company, Nippon Electric Co., Ltd. [Originally in Box 132, Folder 1], 1992 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Litigations - Correspondence, Deposition, Testimony re: Cyrix Corp. and SGS-Thomson Microelectronics Inc. [Originally in Box 132, Folder 2], 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Market Analysis/Data - Newsletters, Correspondence, Reports re: DRAMS, Semiconductor Industry Standard Indicators (Statistics), Graphs, Notes (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 132, Folder 4], 1983-1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Market Analysis/Data - Newsletters, Correspondence, Reports re: DRAMS, Semiconductor Industry Standard Indicators (Statistics), Graphs, Notes (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 132, Folder 5], 1982-1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Matching Gifts Program - Pamphlets, Correspondence, Matching Gifts Forms, Receipts [Originally in Box 132, Folder 6], 1982-1992 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Micro Mask, Inc. - Correspondence, SEC Form 10-K, SEC Information Questionnaires, Employee Stock Purchase Plan (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 133, Folder 1], 1980-1984 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Micro Mask, Inc. - Correspondence, SEC Form 10-K, SEC Information Questionnaires, Stock Option Plan, Indemnification Agreement, Market Survey (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 133, Folder 2], 1984-1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Micro Mask, Inc. - Binder - Correspondence, Annual Report, Operating Reports, Agendas, Minutes, Business Plan, Operating Plan [Originally in Box 133, Folder 3], 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Monterey Bay Aquarium Leadership Council - Correspondence re: New Exhibit Wing, National Geographic Magazine, Issue 1990 [Originally in Box 133, Folder 7], 1994 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering - Correspondence, Newsletters, Programs, Pamphlets, Reports [Originally in Box 134, Folder 1], 1976-1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering - Correspondence, Newsletters, Programs, Draft of Brochure, Symposium Program, Notes [Originally in Box 134, Folder 2], 1989-1998 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering - Nomination and Reference Forms, Correspondence [Originally in Box 134, Folder 3], 1979-1998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering, Industry Advisory Board - Agenda, Minutes, Program, Reports, Booklet re: Global Economy, Global Environment [Originally in Box 134, Folder 4], 1991 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering Industry Advisory Board - National Research Council- Correspondence, Agendas, Science and Engineering Indicator Charts, Notes, Memorandums re: Government-Industry Partnerships, Symposium Pamphlet [Originally in Box 135, Folder 1], 1993-1998 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - National Academies’ Corp. - Board of Directors Meeting Agenda, Minutes, Financial Statements, Financial Reports, Correspondence (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 135, Folder 2], 1990-1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - National Academies’ Corp. - Board of Directors Meeting Agenda, Minutes, Financial Statements, Financial Reports, Correspondence, Report re: Competitive Strength of US Industrial Science and Technology (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 135, Folder 3], 1991-1994 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - National Medal of Technology for Gordon E. Moore - Correspondence re: Nomination, Congratulatory Letters, Articles (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 135, Folder 4], 1988-1991 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Foundation for the National Medals of Science and Technology - Correspondence re: Board of Directors, Agendas, Minutes, Financial Statements, Survey, Booklets (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 136, Folder 1], 1990-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Foundation for the National Medals of Science and Technology - Correspondence re: Board of Directors, Agendas, Minutes, Financial Statements, Booklets, Nomination Forms, Postcards (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 136, Folder 2], 1993-1997 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - National Medal of Technology Binder re: Board of Directors - Brochures, Correspondence, Articles, Business Plan [Originally in Box 136, Folder 3], 1992 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - National Science and Technology Medals Foundation - Magazine, Brochures, Pamphlets, Correspondence, Financial Statements, Media Coverage Reports (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 136, Folder 4], 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - National Science and Technology Medals Foundation - Magazine, Brochures, Pamphlets, Correspondence, Financial Statements, Media Coverage Reports (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 137, Folder 1], 1995-1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - National Nanofabrication Facility at Cornell University - Correspondence, Minutes for Policy Board Meeting and National Research and Resource Facility for Submicron Structures (NRRFSS), NNF User Information Manual, Presentation Slides, Brochures, Annual Report (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 137, Folder 2], 1986-1991 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - National Nanofabrication Facility at Cornell University - Correspondence, Proposals to National Science Foundation for Users Facility (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 137, Folder 3], 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Gordon E. Moore Personal - Correspondence re: Donations, Shareholdings, Stocks, Receipts, Political Contributions Procedures, Copies of Stock Certificates, Articles, Trips [Originally in Box 138, Folder 1], 1975-1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Gordon E. Moore Personal - Correspondence re: Donations, Benefits, CEO of the Year Advisory Board, Officers and Directors Questionnaire, Stocks, Financials, East Texas Pipeline Partnership, Surveys, Shareholdings, Reports, Articles, Investments [Originally in Box 138, Folder 2], 1983-1995 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - US Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4, Statement of Changes in Beneficial Ownership in Securities, Personal Benefit Information for Gordon Moore, Correspondence [Originally in Box 138, Folder 4], 1979-1992 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Peninsula Open Space Trust (POST) - Correspondence, Articles [Originally in Box 139, Folder 2], 1980-1988 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Sandia National Laboratories - Newsletters, Brochures, Pamphlets, Agenda, Research Papers for Gordon Bell Competition [Originally in Box 139, Folder 4], 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Santa Clara University School of Engineering Advisory Board - Minutes, Agenda, Brochure, Correspondence [Originally in Box 139, Folder 5], 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Santa Clara Valley Manufacturing Group - Memos, Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, Correspondence re: Objectives, Annual Reports, Financial Statements, Survey, Report re: Science/Math Enhancement Project [Originally in Box 139, Folder 6], 1991-1997 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - San Jose State University Center for Global Competitiveness - Correspondence [Originally in Box 140, Folder 1], 1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - San Jose State University - Correspondence re: Campaign for College of Business [Originally in Box 140, Folder 2], 1996 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Saxena, Arjun (International Science Company) - Correspondence, Research Paper re: Ultra Large Scale Integrated Circuits [Originally in Box 140, Folder 3], 1996-1997 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Scripps Institution of Oceanography, Director’s Council - Correspondence, Brochures, Reports, Newsletters, Agenda, Notes [Originally in Box 140, Folder 4], 1991-1998 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - SETI Institute (Search for Extraterrestrial Intelligence) - Correspondence, News releases, Brochures, Newsletter [Originally in Box 142, Folder 4], 1994-1998 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Correspondence re: Shareholders, Reports re: Financial Information (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 142, Folder 7], 1983-1984 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Correspondence re: Shareholders, Business Plan, Financial Projections, Appraisal, Spreadsheets, Reports (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 142, Folder 8], 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence re: Financials, Budget Reports, Report re: Salmon Ecosystems, Notes (1 of 4) [Originally in Box 143, Folder 1], 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence re: Financials, Notes, Budget Reports (2 of 4) [Originally in Box 143, Folder 2], 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence re: Financials, Budget Reports, Notes (3 of 4) [Originally in Box 143, Folder 3], 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farms, Inc. - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence re: Financials, Articles, Budget Reports, Reports (4 of 4) [Originally in Box 143, Folder 4], 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Research Institute International Advisory Council - Correspondence, Annual Report, Pamphlets [Originally in Box 143, Folder 5], 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Intel Corp. Technology - Charts re: Chip Size, Components per Chip, Size [Originally in Box 143, Folder 7], circa 1985 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Trade Policy - Presentation of “On America’s National Commercial Interest” by Alan Wolff [Originally in Box 144, Folder 2], 1995 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence re: Directors and Officers [Originally in Box 144, Folder 4], 1995-1997 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Transamerica Corp. Board of Director Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Grand Prix Project and Falcon Project, Minutes re: Pension and Employee Benefits Committee and Audit Committee, Report, Accounting Policies Manual [Originally in Box 144, Folder 5], 1996 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Minutes re: Board of Directors, Audit Committee, Subsidiary Highlights, Booklet re: Corporate Profile, Quarterly Financial Supplement [Originally in Box 144, Folder 6], 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Transamerica Corp. Binder - Organization Charts, Profit Plan, Accounting Policies Manual [Originally in Box 144, Folder 7], 1988-1993 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Transamerica Corp. Investors Seminar Binder - Presentation Slides, Agendas (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 145, Folder 1], November 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Transamerica Corp. Investors Seminar Binder - Presentation Slides, Agendas (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 145, Folder 2], November 1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Audit Charters, Securities and Exchange Commission Form S-3 Registration Statements and Form 10-K, Proxy Statements, Questionnaires, Stock Option Agreement, Compensation Policy (1 of 4) [Originally in Box 145, Folder 3], 1989-1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Annual Report, Pension and Employee Benefits Committee Agenda, Stockholders Meeting Agenda, Finance Committee Meeting Agenda, Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, Proxy Statements, Minutes, Stock Option Agreement, Subsidiary Highlights Booklets, Audit Committee Report (2 of 4) [Originally in Box 145, Folder 4], 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, Form S-3, Proxy Statements, Subsidiary Highlights Reports, Finance Committee Meeting Agenda, Minutes, Audit Committee Report (3 of 4) [Originally in Box 146, Folder 1], 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Audit Committee Agenda, Natal Class Action Settlement Agreement, Audit Committee Report, Minutes, Annual Report to Stockholders, Proxy Statements, Annual Report, Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K (4 of 4) [Originally in Box 146, Folder 2], 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Transamerica Corp. Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4 Statements of Changes of Beneficial Ownership of Securities, SEC Form 10-K (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 146, Folder 3], 1991-1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Transamerica Corp. Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4 Statements of Changes of Beneficial Ownership of Securities, SEC Form 10-K, Stock Option Plan, Proxy Statements (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 146, Folder 4], 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Agenda re: Audit Committee Meeting, Report on Investment Performance of Pension Assets [Originally in Box 147, Folder 1], 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Directors Meeting, Subsidiary Highlights Report [Originally in Box 147, Folder 2], 1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Transamerica Corp. - Correspondence, Agenda re: Board of Directors Meeting, Accounting Policies Manual, Subsidiary Highlights Report, Quarterly Financial Supplement [Originally in Box 147, Folder 3], 1994 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Transamerica Corp. Board of Directors Reports re: Audit Committee, Financial Statement [Originally in Box 147, Folder 4], 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - United Way of Santa Clara County - Correspondence re: Alexis de Tocqueville Society, Foothill-De Anza Community College Chancellor’s Scholar Program, Reports re: Strategic Plan, Pamphlets, Bay Area Council Pamphlet, Presentation Notes [Originally in Box 147, Folder 5], 1988-1996 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - University of California Berkeley Advisory Board - Correspondence, Notes, Campaign Pamphlets re: New Materials Initiative [Originally in Box 147, Folder 6], 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - University of California San Diego Advisory Board - Correspondence, Agenda re: Industrial Advisory Committee, Booklets [Originally in Box 147, Folder 7], 1990-1992 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - University of California Santa Barbara Advisory Board - Reports, Agendas, Research re: Compound Semiconductor Research Laboratories, Pamphlets [Originally in Box 147, Folder 8], 1993 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Varian Associates - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4 Statements of Changes of Beneficial Ownership of Securities, SEC Form 10-K, Form 5 Certification, Correspondence re: Stock Options (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 148, Folder 1], 1990-1993 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Varian Associates - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 4 Statements of Changes of Beneficial Ownership of Securities, SEC Form 10-K, Form 5 Certification, Correspondence re: Stock Options (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 148, Folder 2], 1994-1998 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Varian Associates - Board of Directors Binder- Minutes re: Organization & Compensation Committee, Nominating Committee, Board of Directors Meeting, Technology and Environment Committee, Finance Committee, Bylaws, Audit Plan, Code of Business Ethics, Annual Reports [Originally in Box 148, Folder 3], 1987-1991 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Varian Associates - Director Manual - Agendas, Minutes, Committees, Organizational Charts, Policies re: Compensation, Insurance, Securities Law, Charter Documents, Annual Reports [Originally in Box 148, Folder 4], 1993 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Varian Associates - Correspondence re: Industrial Security Agreement, Securities and Exchange Commission Questionnaires, Form 4, Proxy Statements, Board of Directors Meeting Agendas and Minutes, Agendas and Minutes re: Technology and Environment Committee (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 148, Folder 5], 1989-1992 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Varian Associates - Correspondence, Agenda and Minutes re: Organization & Compensation Committee, Nominating Committee, Board of Directors Meeting, Technology and Environment Committee, Finance Committee, Shields Complaint Case, Proxy Statements (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 149, Folder 1], 1992-1993 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Varian Associates - Correspondence, Agenda and Minutes re: Nominating Committee, Board of Directors Meeting, Proxy Statements, SEC Questionnaire, Form 10-K, Annual Reports (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 149, Folder 2], 1993-1997 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Varian Associates - Agenda, Minutes re: Board of Directors Meeting, Correspondence, Resumes [Originally in Box 149, Folder 3], 1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Varian Associates - Agenda, Minutes re: Technology and Environmental Committee Meeting, Organization and Compensation Committee Meeting, Audit Committee, Nominating Committee, Board of Directors, Correspondence [Originally in Box 149, Folder 4], 1994 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Varian Associates - Agenda, Minutes re: Technology and Environmental Committee Meeting, Organization and Compensation Committee Meeting, Audit Committee, Nominating Committee, Board of Directors, Correspondence, Annual Reports, SEC Form 10-K, Survey [Originally in Box 150, Folder 1], 1993 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Varian Associates - Agenda, Minutes re: Board of Directors Meeting, Technology and Environmental Committee Meeting, Organization and Compensation Committee Meeting, Audit Committee, Nominating Committee, Director Manual, Correspondence, Minutes [Originally in Box 150, Folder 2], 1996 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Varian Associates re: Shields Complaint Suit - Correspondence, Complaint Summaries [Originally in Box 150, Folder 3], 1988 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Veritas Corp. - Business Development Plans, Correspondence [Originally in Box 150, Folder 4], 1995 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - Correspondence [Originally in Box 150, Folder 5], 1984-1985 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Cards to Gordon Moore [Originally in Box 151], 2001 (Box 72)
  - Binder of Business Cards [Originally in Box 152], undated (Box 73)
  - Rolodex of Gordon Moore [Originally in Box 153], undated (Box 74)
  - Oversize Box [Originally in Box 154], 1958-2005 (Box 75)
- Series 4: Photographs and Slides, 1964-2001
  Initially there were seven binders of 35mm slides that were used in presentations given by Moore. The binders were removed and the slides are now housed in new protective holders in their original order. Also in this series are photographs, graphs, and presentation slides of various Intel devices, staff, and processes. One box contains photographs that were pulled from Series II Chronological Files and Series III Alphabetical Files and within each folder are separation sheets notating their original locations.
  - 35mm slides: Miscellaneous [Originally in Box 155, Folder 1], undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 35mm slides: NY Analyst Meeting [Originally in Box 155, Folder 2], 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 35mm slides: RNN Honeywell [Originally in Box 155, Folder 3], circa 1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 35mm: Shareholders Mtg [Originally in Box 155, Folder 4], 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 35mm: Dataquest Conference [Originally in Box 155, Folder 5], 1977 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 35mm: National Computer Conference [Originally in Box 155, Folder 6], 1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 35mm International Solid State Circuits Conference [Originally in Box 155, Folder 7], 1979 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 35mm Intel Corp Annual Shareholder's Meeting [Originally in Box 155, Folder 8], 1979 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - 35mm Schools Talks [Originally in Box 155, Folder 9], 1977 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - 35mm Montgomery Securities Investment Conference [Originally in Box 155, Folder 10], 1979 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - 35mm slides from NY Analyst Meeting [Originally in Box 156, Folder 1], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - American Association for Advancement of Science Meeting [Originally in Box 156, Folder 2], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Intel Annual Shareholders Meeting Andrew Grove slides [Originally in Box 156, Folder 3], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Intel Annual Shareholders Meeting Andrew Grove slides [Originally in Box 156, Folder 4], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Rosen Research Conference (New Orleans) [Originally in Box 156, Folder 5], undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Dataquest Slides [Originally in Box 156, Folder 5], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Society of Financials, Houston Analysts [Originally in Box 156, Folder 7], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Financial Community Presentations pre-Debenture [Originally in Box 156, Folder 8], 1980 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Brookings institute [Originally in Box 156, Folder 9], 1981 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Intel Annual Shareholders Meeting [Originally in Box 156, Folder 10], 1981 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Intel Annual Shareholders Meeting, 1981 Andrew Grove slides [Originally in Box 156, Folder 11] (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Electrochemical Society, Minneapolis [Originally in Box 157, Folder 1], 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - New York Society of Security Analysts [Originally in Box 157, Folder 2], 1981 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Intel Annual Shareholder's Meeting (Note: catalogue says Intel Annual Board meeting) [Originally in Box 157, Folder 3], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - LFRUT Meeting in Europe [Originally in Box 157, Folder 4], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Distributor Presidents Conference [Originally in Box 157, Folder 5], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Graduate School of Business [Originally in Box 157, Folder 6], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - AAAS Meeting; Computers in Science Meeting [Originally in Box 157, Folder 7], 1982 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Intel Annual Shareholder Meeting (Note; Not board meeting) [Originally in Box 157, Folder 8], 1983 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference [Originally in Box 157, Folder 9], 1983 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Wyle Laboratories Presentation [Originally in Box 157, Folder 10], 1984 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Intel Annual Stockholders Meeting (Note: Not board meeting) [Originally in Box 157, Folder 11], 1984 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - IEEE Centennial Conference [Originally in Box 157, Folder 12], undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Intel Annual Stockholders meeting Andrew Grove Slides [Originally in Box 158, Folder 1], 1985 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - LFRUT Meeting in Europe [Originally in Box 158, Folder 2], 1985 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - New York Society of Security Analysts [Originally in Box 158, Folder 4], 1986 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Wyle Laboratories Presentation [Originally in Box 158, Folder 5], 1986 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Changing semiconductor Industry - Japan Trip [Originally in Box 158, Folder 6], 1986 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - National Sales Conference [Originally in Box 158, Folder 7], 1987 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - National Financial Computer and Automation Conference [Originally in Box 158, Folder 8], 1987 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference [Originally in Box 158, Folder 9], 1987 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Univ of Illinois Beckman Lecture [Originally in Box 158, Folder 10], 1987 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Caltech Lecture on Future Trends in Microcomputing [Originally in Box 158, Folder 11], 1988 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Japan Financial Presentation [Originally in Box 158, Folder 13], undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - IEEE Reliability Physics Meeting, Monterey [Originally in Box 158, Folder 14], 1988 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - AEA Oregon Council Meeting [Originally in Box 158, Folder 15], 1989 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Irish Plant site Announcement [Originally in Box 158, Folder 16], 1989 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Intel Corporation UK Fair [Originally in Box 158, Folder 17], 1989 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Distributor Presidents Conference [Originally in Box 158, Folder 18], 1989 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Misc slides (portraits of GEM) [Originally in Box 159, Folder 1], undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - AEA Oregon Council Meeting [Originally in Box 159, Folder 2], 1989 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Financial Meetings in Europe [Originally in Box 159, Folder 6], 1990 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - IEEE Symposium on VLSI technology [Originally in Box 159, Folder 7], 1990 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - New Mexico Chamber of Commerce [Originally in Box 159, Folder 8], 1990 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Distributor President's Conference [Originally in Box 159, Folder 9], 1990 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - SIA Meeting (copyright SIA) [Originally in Box 159, Folder 10], undated (Box 80, Folder 7)